Erfan Ghezelbash

E-mail: erfan.ghezelbash@gmail.com Website: https://www.linkedin.com/in/erfanghezelbash

Phone: +31643477531 Address: Groningen, Netherlands

Summary

Graduated in software engineering with more than eight years of experience in web programming, intrested and active in Blockchain, Fintech and any other edge technology. Able to build projects from scratch and implement MVP systems with more than 7 successful experiences.

Work experience

Youwe Jul 2021 — Present

Magento Developer

• Working on various e-commerce projects doing development and maintenance.

• Mainly working on Magento 2 projects as a full-stack developer.

Excoino Jun 2019 — Jun 2021

Senior Software Engineer

- Change and improve about 80% of the project with the aim of converting the MVP model into enterprise software within a year
- Redesigned data model and software architecture, which increased system performance 6 times
- Increase the test coverage of sensitive parts of the system from zero to 47%
- Support 8 Junior Developers in 18 months by recommending, coaching and routing for research

Dunab Ertebat LLC

Sep 2017 — May 2019

Senior Software Engineer

- Launching 4 startup projects in various fields of finance, cryptocurrency, human resources and project management
- Work on three programming languages: PHP, Java and Nodejs to implement projects
- Interview with more than 100 people in one year and recruit 11 technical staff for the company
- Coaching, routing and assisting younger techies

Jul 2015 — Sep 2017

Co-founder and Software Developer

- Co-founding and developing 3 startup / experimental projects in two years
- Delivery and support of more than 20 customer-oriented projects in the form of an 8-member team
- Providing 4 long-term training courses for web programming enthusiasts for a total of about 60 people

Fara Computer

Gilas

Feb 2013 — May 2015

Junior Web Developer

 Development and support of company website and two partner companies using WordPress tool as well as Laravel framework

Erfan Ghezelbash

Fara Computer

Software Solutions Support

Jan 2012 — Feb 2013

Fara Computer

Software Internship

Jun 2011 — Jan 2012

Education

BSc in Software Engineering Sep 2008 — Jun 2013

Payame Noor University

Languages

- English Full Professional Proficiency
- Persian/Farsi Native or Bilingual Proficiency
- French Elementry Proficiency

Skills

PHP Laravel

Blockchain

Solidity

Cryptocurrency

SQL

Teamwork

Technical Coaching

Working under Pressure

Fran Ghezelhash